Welcome back to another episode of New
Orleans. Football presented by Loft 18.
Day two of the draft coming up. Day one
recap here. We're going to be breaking
it all down. We're going to have
everything you need to know about the
Jordan Tyson pick and what to expect in
the upcoming rounds. Hopefully we hit on
those and uh set you up with some
insight heading into night two. Keep it
locked to New Orleans football all
throughout. We have our live updates
going there, live chat going. you can
come in, hang out with us, get our
analysis as it as it happens, uh we're
posting there more than we are anywhere
else. So, if you want our up to the
minute, up to the second thoughts and
our insights and what we're hearing and
the rumors and all that stuff, that is
the place to be throughout the night.
And then we're getting you the updates
on what people are saying and interviews
and all that stuff, too. So, definitely
the place to be for that. And then also,
our mock draft machine is updated with
all the round one picks in it. So, you
can jump on there right now. Run your
simulations for the rest of the draft
going through it. And then tonight, if
we set it up right, and I think we did,
it'll be uh populating the picks as they
happen in the machine, so you can get
accurate scenarios as picks are actually
happening. Um, and those should be in
there probably before Goodell even
announces them. So, get on New Orleans
Football, do all that. Make sure you're
at Loft 18. They got four locations.
Breward, Baton Rouge, uh, Meia,
Mandavville, all of those. And if you
are going somewhere, do it in a car that
you get from my guy Map Hours. He has
dealerships all throughout the region,
all throughout the country. Um,
definitely all throughout the state.
He'll get you right. He'll get you the
best car, best prices, best of
everything. And for the best of
everything today, Mike Triplet joins us
to break down the draft. So, our first
topic presented by PJs because every
single day should start with PJs. Could
the Saints have done any better in round
one?
Well, you know, I'm a Caleb DS guy, so I
say yes, but they had their choice of
Caleb DS, so they don't think so. Um,
the the the two names that stand out
that I think were in their cloud, in
their bubble, uh, went two picks before
them, and that's Sunny Styles went one
pick before them. Monsor Delane went two
picks before them. I I think there were
scenarios where that could have been the
pick. Um, I'll I'll ask your thoughts on
how you think that would have gone and
and if you think that would have been
better. I like Tyson as much as I like
Styles or or Delane, though. I mean,
because if if the talent is close, the
fit is the best of those three for me.
Um, but my favorite thing of all is that
they didn't trade up. I I I was
admittedly nervous. There might be there
might I know Arizona won it out of that
pick three and I thought, what if the
Saints make them the best offer? What if
this happens? My favorite thing about uh
night one was that they made their pick
at pick eight. And obviously I'm a lot
it just makes me feel so much better
about the team. Receiver was one of
those positions we've been talking about
a lot whether they did it round one or
round two or round three or went after
the draft and added another veteran.
They they were a man short there. And
now you just feel better about the whole
receiving core. You feel better about a
you feel better about Shuck. You feel
better about Vle. You feel better about
Pulk. You feel better about the entire
offense. Um, it's great when you can get
a talented player uh who who makes like
who feels like he makes the entire unit
go. Now,
>> based on my my information that that I
have, Sunonny Styles would have been a
conversation. Dellay would not have been
a conversation. It was Tyson 7,000 out
of 7,000 times over him. Tyson would
have been 7,000 out of 7,000 times over
Carell Tate. And they obviously didn't
want down. Sunny Styles would have been
a conversation. And I I don't know how
that one would have turned out. I think
Styles was graded pretty highly, but I
know Jordan Tyson was an early target.
Um, you know, if Arvel Reese had been
there or Jeremiah Love, I think those
would have been maybe, you know, I think
the pick goes differently. Styles, I'm
not sure. That was one that was kind of
over the last week. I was kind of
hearing things about that going back and
forth and there being conversations in
that delay would have been the fallback
option if they got jumped and I think
there were scenarios where you know that
could have that could have easily
happened and I think Tate going at four
kind of locked this in to where they
they got him at their spot because I
think that changes what the Giants do at
five and five was kind of the pressure
point where you started to think maybe
maybe Tyson could go and that would have
been a spot for him. And then, you know,
I was hearing from people from the
Giants that that they thought that, too.
So, I think that's maybe where it played
out. Now, I do find it interesting and
I'm not like obviously
there's the Jordan Tyson the injury risk
and the injury risk is real and that's
obviously a huge part of this. There is
one piece of this and I'm not I'm not
guaranteeing the man's going to stay
healthy. I'm not guaranteeing like I you
know obviously you make this pick and
know that there are injury risks and if
they pop up you bet wrong and you know
that's that's a major misvaluation. I do
find it interesting and granted I do
know that he didn't miss games in
college and all that but I but I just
want to say this like as people frame
these arguments about safe verse not
safe. Caleb Donalds has a knee injury
today.
I want I mean that that had to have been
a factor because he went 11th. The
Giants passed on him twice. I mean
that's that's that must have been a real
factor.
>> I don't know if it is or it isn't, but
it's just it isn't like one, you know
what I mean? Like there's that too. Like
that was something teams were evaluating
throughout this as well. So I mean that
that's just part of it. I just think as
as we have these conversations just
everybody keep that in mind too. Like
that's the thing as well. I don't think
it was an issue for the Saints. So, I'm
not saying that like this isn't, oh,
like they're salulting some rumor or
something. Like, no. Like, they checked
it. They thought it was clean. I think I
said it on the show a while ago that
that that wasn't a part of the
evaluation. I think they just think
Jordan Tyson is a guy that can change
their team, can change their offense.
And I I happen to agree with that. If
he's healthy, holy man. Like, you
watch this guy play football, he's a
very, very good football player.
>> Yes. And look, the the injury concern,
I've said this a few times now, and I'm
sure people have rolled my eyes and and
and I I I gotta say it the best way, but
I genuinely believe that the Saints want
to take risk out of the number eight
pick in the draft. like that. I don't
have to stretch and and be in their back
pocket or be a company man to say that I
genuinely believe the Saints care about
getting that pick right and don't want
to just roll the dice on someone who has
a 5050 chance of playing. Okay. So,
their medical evaluations could be
wrong. They have been wrong before, but
I think it's something that they
probably very very strongly considered
and very diligently considered. Um, I
don't think they're ah injuries, who who
cares? Let someone else that um, and I
loved Tyson's answer about it because
look, here's the thing about the
hamstring. The knee doesn't bother me.
That was years ago. And, and look, knee
injuries do happen. Uh, I don't think he
has like a chronic issue like Ryan Ramch
had or anything like that. He tore his
knee up one time, years ago, and he's
come back and played some incredible
football since then. The hamstring
injury is the one that was concerning
because it lingered. like it happened in
October, reinjured it when he tried to
come back and play, was still injured in
the pre-draft process, and people were
starting to think, what's wrong with
this guy? But hamstring injuries, we've
got, you know, a history of people who
have had hamstring injuries and then
have gotten together with with teams of
doctors and and trainers and NFL teams
and come up with a plan. We were talking
about the the Jackson Smith and Jigba
story, how he figured about his shoe
size. I loved that Tyson had answers for
it last night. We asked him about it a
couple different ways. I I asked a
follow-up question. I said, "Did you
guys learn anything?" And he said,
"Yeah, we learned my hips are tight.
That it's actually more of a hip problem
than hamstring problem. My glutes
weren't activating. Uh because I put so
much power on my hips, I'm putting a lot
of pressure, so we're getting my hips
loose." Like, I mean, he's figuring out
plans to attack this. But before that,
he said he's a very excited guy. Talked
about his work ethic over and over
again. very excitedly rattled off. I'm
gonna give myself the best opportunity
to stay on the field and be as healthy
as possible. I'm gonna do everything in
the weight room. I'm gonna do everything
in nutrition. I'm gonna have my own
chef. I'm gonna get my massage on the
same day every week. I'm going to have
my reg regimen sewed down to a tea. I'm
going to give myself the best
opportunity. We do play football, but
I'm going to give myself the best shot
possible. He's he's attacking this.
They're attacking this. Like they sold
me that like this is not a guy like I
don't think he's gonna be lazy. I don't
think he's going to be overweight. I
don't think he's got chronic injury
problems. The hamstring thing came up
once and and now they're making it like
their absolute all to make sure that
that's not a consistent problem for him.
So maybe it will be, but I'm not I'm not
like like what did they do? They threw
this pick away. I'm not like that at
all.
>> No, I mean it's obviously something
that's is going to be judged against and
it's going to be a sore spot if he ever
misses a practice or or anything like
that. And I I said it in the video last
night like he he could go through a year
>> and in year two if he gets an injury
people are going to be like ah like he's
>> you know and and it's and it's probably
going to be uh one of those things. So
it's going to be what he's judged
against. He's going to be judged against
Caleb DS. It just kind of is what it is.
But you know
>> if I was making the pick I would have
made the same pick. And I can't sit here
and lie and say anything about it. I
mean I I just kind of worked through my
process where I was like man Lemon's
like really good after the catch and he
doesn't miss time and then you just keep
watching. It's like this guy is so much
better than the other receivers and I'm
inherently a risk taker and I'm willing
to set myself on fire to find success.
Like that's just how I think about
things. I I you know it could obviously
be a wrong pick. But here's my thing. I
like the pick and this this is
continuing uh the conversation presented
by Bobby Aber's Cajun Cannon Restaurant.
I like the pick because I like the idea
of where this team is at.
My thing really just came down to, and
it's this is going to be the dumbest,
simplest thing I've ever said on the
show, is that I I wanted them to get a
TD getter. Like, I just did. I wanted
them to get a guy that scored
touchdowns. And I feel like they were
really maybe one player away on one side
of the ball. And I feel like maybe they
went and got that one player to take
them to a place where this is why they
win games. And I, you know, adding Caleb
DS, you're kind of, you still got holes
on offense. you're still looking at that
depth chart and obviously you could have
addressed it at 42 or 73 or or whatever.
Um, but you're looking at that depth
chart and you're still looking at insert
a name, Pulk, Palmer, Typton, whoever.
And maybe one of those guys really hit
and and they become really good, Bub
Means. Maybe one of them hit the leap.
But now I'm looking at the depths chart
and 11 personnel going across. I I'm
looking at Chris Lave, Jordan Tyson,
Devon Bailey, Achan, Alvin Kamara,
Kendra Miller is the two guys behind it
there at tight end. I'm looking at Jawan
Johnson. If I want to go to 12, it's
Jawan Johnson and and and Fano and Tyson
and Chris Ave and Achan. If I want to go
to, you know, 22, I got those two guys
and I can choose between my my three
receivers. Like, that's a that's the
reason you're going to win games. You
got David Edwards on there now. Go draft
another offensive line lineman
somewhere. Maybe get some competition
going. Like, the offense is to me, if
Tyler Shock is who we think he is, it's
a legitimate legitimate strength. I I
think a guy like Jordan Tyson can take
Tyler Shuck from I don't like I don't
even know where where you'd rank him
right now, but that could be the
difference between, you know, going from
17 to 12 to 11 to 10. Like I I think a
guy like that elevates your quarterback.
So to me, that was my reason. Like we we
were kind of I think me and you like you
had Downs, Tyson, I had Tyson DS, and
you could flip-flop them either way. And
I felt like their defense was built and
that was the one guy that that okay,
they're going to win every game because
of Caleb. I actually think Jordan Tyson
changes their their fortunes if you tell
me he's playing 15 games next year. I
>> I agree with that. I mean, part of the
reason, look, I did like DS more. Um and
and I'm still betting on DS's career. Um
um
>> yeah,
>> he's going to be a great player.
>> Check back here, you know, 10 years from
now when I said I think he'll have the
most all pros of anyone in this draft
class. I I still make that bet. Um and I
would have liked Reese or Bailey. Uh, I
would not have wanted them to trade up,
but what Reese felt a five, all of a
sudden, all of a sudden, if the Giants
make a different pick there and the
Saints trade up to six and get Arbell
Reese, I might have been even more
excited about that. Um, but I will say I
genuinely don't think there's anything
to your point you just made, I don't
think there was another position, and I
don't think there was another player
that was more transformative for me.
Like even even another pass rusher, I'd
have been like, "Yes, they needed that."
And and I still think Cam Jordan should
come back. That that might have
prevented it from happening. But I don't
know that one more pass rusher added to
Chase Young and Carl Anderson and Cam
Jordan would have made me be like now
the whole off defense is better. It
would have just made me feel better
about the pass rush. This makes the
whole offense better. There was not
another position they could have drafted
that made an entire unit better. Caleb
downs a little bit. I think they do need
that general of the secondary to make
the whole secondary better. But but
receiver was thin and scary. We love a
we're excited about what Vle could do.
Hopefully they can both stay healthy.
Even if those guys played every game and
didn't have the third receiver, you'd
still be like h they are a weapon short.
Like this makes the whole offense
better. No other pick they could have
made in the first round would have
immediately transformed an entire unit
and and no receiver would have been as
exciting. I I would have liked the
Cardell tape pick. Um I would have liked
a Mai Lemon pick, but this this is the
most exciting one if he's going to be on
the field for sure.
>> My uh my hot take for this this class,
Jeremiah Love aside, who who I think is
is going to be the best player. I kind
of think Sunny Styles might end up being
the best player out of the top 10. Like
if let's let's start where Downs go. 11
11 or 12.
>> Downs went 11, I think.
>> So, let's go to
>> top 10. Yeah,
>> downs up. I I think Sunonny Styles is
going to be the guy. I just I don't
know. I think he I think he's going to
be the guy. I think he's going to be the
guy. I think he's going to
>> I think he's going to be a better
three-level player than Caleb DS. I just
I think they're going to end up being
used very similarly. And I think Sunonny
Styles is I again, it's the upside thing
though. Like that's the gambler. like
the gambler like Caleb DS is a safer
pick. He's Sunonny Styles is the the
dangerous pick. But
>> yeah,
>> man, his his
>> they didn't draft him, so I don't need
to like go into the whole thing, but um
like his his improvement year over year,
like he went from missing every tackle
like an Isaiah Simmons missed like every
tackle his last year, college, junior
year, Sunonny Styles like couldn't
tackle, senior year, he didn't miss any
tackles. Like his improvement year over
year over year, I I think he has a
chance to be incredible. Like it would
have been a fascinating conversation if
both those guys were on the board
together cuz I know how much they like
Tyson. I know how much man there was so
much energy behind this. Yesterday I was
getting texts from like guys on the team
um that were just over the like just
like they they like there's real energy
on that offense right now. So just that
alone I think really really is a nice
improvement and it should be about Shuck
right now. This whole team should be
about the build for Tyler Shuck and and
all that stuff. I I think this is a move
that makes Chris Olive a better wide
receiver. Um I I'm betting on him. Go
hit FanDuel or whatever. Like I I would
bet on him to have a career year this
year. If you're telling me he plays
every game, the concerning part about
this is is that Chris has missed time.
Devon misses time and we've seen Jordan
Tyson miss time. Chris was healthy last
year. I mean, everybody gets hurt. It's
football. It happens. But like when you
see it, it becomes concerning. It's just
one of them things. And it can be a fair
conversation or it could be an unfair
conversation. Um, you know, I I will say
like my comp for him was like Odell
Beckham. Odell had those issues and, you
know, was came into the league with it.
Um, you know, Marawn had major hamstring
issues. That wasn't really a real
problem for him until the end of his
tenure when I think maybe it just wasn't
I I don't want to say what I want to
say, but like I just kind of think that,
you know,
>> you don't think Marshon had the I'm
going to go to my massage every day. I'm
going to go to the weight room every
day. I'm going to go to the nutritionist
every day all off all season long.
>> I just I just feel like Vle might jump
on it a little bit or not Vaylee. Uh
Tyson might jump on it a little bit
different, you know. So, um yeah, I just
I just think Yeah, look, I like I like
the pick. I like the player. I like the
talent. The thing I can't see is I can't
see it. And I I think it's kind of you
got to judge it from that and you got to
evaluate it from that, but I also think
it's kind of unfair to assume before bad
happens as well. Um it's a bet that's
going to define him. But I will say
this, like if you're an organization
with job security
and you aren't drafting from a scared
position,
>> I like the idea of chasing the talent
because you you have the the courage and
the and the gusto in the in the ability
to try to really hit the big boom. And
man, go for the big boom. Like if you
can win a Super Bowl like and there's a
move that gets you closer to it, go for
it. And you know, I think drafting
scared and all that is uh it's just not
a good way to be.
>> No, I think
>> you got to be smart.
>> Yeah, of course. And yeah, I mean, you
could you could frame the injury thing
from another perspective. Like now you
feel a little safer about a Vle and
Tyson and just hope hope they rotate
their injuries if any of them miss time.
But you're double backed up now. You
know,
>> it is a scary thing though like the
first time like I you know, I don't want
to act like it's nothing either. Like
the first like if he gets hurt in camp,
it's going to be like oh my god. you
know, just immediately thought, yeah, I
mean, so it's a very
>> they they got to get it right. That's
the thing that you just put a top 10
pick into it, you got to get it right.
But I mean, what does that even mean?
Because
>> the security I don't know. It's like
let's just wait to see. Let's let's have
that conversation if it happens.
>> The Giants took uh Manuoa u
>> Maga. No, but it's with an end. Manuoa
Ma Noah.
>> Maago. Yeah. Back injury.
>> Took him at 10. And there's injury
concerns surrounding him, too. Um, you
know, some teams some teams do. I mean,
risk is inherent in in the draft. Risk
is inherent in the draft. Um, uh, but
hopefully hopefully hopefully Marshon
Latimore is the example. Marshon
Latimore fell because of hamstring
concerns and they were not an issue
early in his career. Um, so hopefully
it's more a case of that than it is.
What What are the horror stories that
that come to mind for people whether
it's Marcus Davenport or or Pton Turner
or um Kendrey Miller?
Yeah. Look, I also thought it was
interesting, too. Um, we were watching
or we I was watching um clips of uh
the Bleacher Report show and Malik
Neighbors was on there and they had
Malik Neighbors uh they were like, you
know, what if he d what if they draft a
wide receiver at five? And he's like,
no, like they'll end up paying that guy
more than me. And like he was against
it. And then meanwhile, like I'm
comfortable saying this cuz he put it
out in public like Chris was celebrated
in public like and I talked to him last
night and he was just like, "Man, like I
I'm I can't wait for this. Like I've
been waiting to get a guy like this on
the team and all this stuff." So it's uh
just a completely different mindset.
Like I I like that so much from Chris. I
liked his reaction from that so much.
Like he's fighting for his he don't
care. Like he just wants to win games,
you know, privately. we've had
conversations over the year like it just
you know he wants to win so bad and like
his reaction to this it made me like you
know it was just like seeing that and
like I don't know it was just different
and I like his reaction to it like I
think that makes for a really good
locker room. Um and we saw Chris kind of
like emerge into some of that stuff last
year with just how he like talked about
Rattler and that I I like I like where
Chris is at. I like where his head's at.
He's going to get paid and I like that
he was excited about this and it wasn't
like this this guy's coming to take
something from me or something like
that. like he's looking at like, "No,
this guy's going to help me. We're going
to win games. I'm going to get open.
We're going to win." And it's going to
feel like Ohio State maybe and not, you
know, the last several years of of, you
know, the the doldrum since he's been
drafted.
>> Ohio State receivers do know the the
value of having two other like all next.
They really do. Malik Neighbors also on
that podcast was pissed that the Giants
didn't take Caleb DS and then uh Caleb
DS went to the Cowboys and he's like now
I got to face this guy twice a year. So
yeah,
>> at least Malik Neighbors was on was on
my team with Caleb DS. But I agree.
>> Yeah. Um all right, let's hit a quick
break and we'll be right back.
>> Welcome to Loft 18, your favorite local
sports bar.
The economy has been tough and
entertainment hasn't been as affordable
as it once was. We get it. That's why
we're changing the whole game with lower
menu prices, all new deals, and brand
new promotions.
Great service, good vibes, and
consistent food. Here at Loft 18, the
experience is built around you.
Rous's Markets is noted best grocery
store in New Orleans, best grocery store
in Baton Rouge, Mississippi, GF Coast,
Tibido, Homa, Hammond, Lake Charles,
Mobile, year after year. Thank you for
choosing us. Best grocery store on the
Gulf Coast. Number one. Thank you.
>> Thank you. The number one grocery store
>> in Mississippi, Alabama,
>> Louisiana. A million customers a week
can't be wrong. Welcome to Rouses.
Here at New Orleans Football, we get
every day started with PJs and you
should too. We are proud to be partnered
with them. They have the best coffee,
the best pastries, and locations all
over the city and state. PJ's Coffee.
Check them out. Get your day started
with them. There's a ton of great things
about living in New Orleans, but one of
the worst things about living in New
Orleans is the soaring insurance costs.
Whether it's your house, your flood,
your car, somebody's always trying to
get in your pocket. Somebody's always
trying to raise prices. That's why you
need a partner like Shaw Bear Insurance,
the Airheart Agency to have your back.
Every 6 months, I get a call from them.
Hey, look, your car insurance is going
up. This is what we can do to lower it.
Do you want to do it? Yeah, of course I
want to do it. Same thing when my home
insurance comes up. Hey, do you want to
bring this price down? Yes, I want to
bring my price down. They're watching it
so I don't have to. Somebody's trying to
get deeper in my pockets. They're
stopping people from getting deeper into
my pockets. You need people like that
because it means money in your pockets.
So, do business with Shaw Bear
Insurance, the Airheart Agency. Make
sure you're looking for the Airheart
Agency branch. That's the one we use.
They look out for me. I use them long
before they ever advertised on this
podcast. They save me money. They'll
save you money. Tell them I've sent you.
You ever take a bite of something and
immediately think, "Yeah, I'm coming
back for this." Bobby Aber's Cajun
Cannon Restaurant just added some new
dishes, and man, they crushed it. The
shrimp and crawfish pistollettes,
golden, and stuffed with bold Cajun
flavor. Fried oyster tacos, crispy,
fresh with the perfect kick. And the
soft shell crab alfredo, creamy, rich,
and absolutely worth the order. They're
open 7 days a week, and they deliver
late. Bobby Aberers's Cajun Cannon
Restaurant. Delicious food, superior
service. New Orleans football is proud
to be in business with our longtime
partners at Hardh High Punch Strawberry
Whiskey and Chilton County Peach. When
you're out and about in your favorite
stores, your favorite bars, your
favorite restaurants, look up on the
shelf, look for the red bottle, look for
the orange bottle, see if there's a
gator on it. If there is, that's your
drink. It's going to taste right. It's
going to get you right. Look for
hardhide in your favorite stores, bars,
and restaurants.
Welcome back to New Orleans. Football
presented by Loft 18. Our next topic is
presented by Shabar Insurance, the
Airheart Agency. Um,
first of all, before we hit this, was
there any pick that was crazy to you in
round one? Anything that stood out to
you?
>> I mean, it's uh Tai Simpson. The Shawn
McVey stuff is wild today. Shawn McVey
is pissed. Like, there's no hiding it.
Like, there's no, "Oh, no, that was
taken." Remember the time they showed
the Saints draft room photo and
everybody was sitting in the back like
this and everybody tried to be like,
"Look how mad they all are." With a
still photo. Um that that was that was
misinterpreted uh from a fan base
looking for looking for ghosts. Shawn
McVey is actually pissed. Like there's
clips of Shawn McVey like on a K. Adams
interview a couple weeks ago being like,
"Oh, uh you he told Kay Adams you
studied Ty Simpson more than me. There's
a lot of other players I like better in
this draft." And and like the post the
press conference last night, he's just
like given one-word answers with steam
coming out of his ears. Like Shawn McVey
is pissed about that pick.
>> I didn't know how to I didn't know there
was all that context. I only saw the one
thing where where he was talking to him
on the phone and there he was like,
"Let's go make history." And Sean's
like, "Yeah, all right. Have a good
one." Like basically like damn. And I
didn't know people were making too much
of it or not, but I I guess not. Like I
didn't see all the other stuff. Their
whole approach to everything
>> I don't hate that. Like the Rams are the
perfect kind of team to I didn't
necessarily believe this during the Drew
Brees era. Everyone was like Shawn
Peyton, you know, should have had a
backup plan. It's easier said than done.
You can't like be picking 27th every
year and and guarantee your backup plan
for Drew Brees. So like I like that the
Rams now like if they believe in this
guy, I like that Matthew Stafford
probably only has two years left in his
career. Um but Shay didn't seem to show
me is probably like well let's win a
Super Bowl. We have the 13th pick.
Hopefully, we'll never have the 13th
pick again for the rest of my coaching
career. And we're using it on on a guy
that I don't even think is going to beat
out Stson Bennett for the backup job.
>> The uh Yeah,
I feel like it's the right spot for him.
I I didn't feel like he was ready for
the NFL. So, I mean that I think that's
a good spot for him to be able to go and
stay. I mean, obviously the Rams do a
great job. Their whole approach to
everything is very weird to me. how
McVey doesn't get involved in anything
really with the draft. Uh they don't go
to the the combine, him or the GM. They
don't do 30 visits, by the way. Shut the
hell up about the 30 visit thing. Like
that's over. Um and that was never true.
But like that can go away now. Thank
God. Uh such an annoying storyline
because it was just like factually
false. Uh but
and like I I I get mad at that cuz I
take a lot of like effort to inform
people and then when it's just like
you're misinforming that makes that's
just like you know my life's work is
informing trying to accurately. Um but
yeah it's just very weird very weird how
they do it all. And then they draft
really well though like I was looking at
their list today and it's like they they
got a lot of hits so like their approach
works. is just different than
everybody's. But boy, like if it weren't
hitting, that would be so open for
criticism. Um, but for me, and I and I'm
reluctant to say this, um, our guy
spotted him. He knew who he was. He seen
him at the Senior Bowl.
>> He loved Caleb Banks.
>> Adam hit it. But man, boy, do I think
that was a wild pick. That was a wild
pick at that rate. like it's just a wild
pick to let a team with no GM draft a
guy with injury concerns um at that spot
that high. It's just for another team I
I wouldn't feel that way for Minnesota,
a team that does not have their GM to do
that is kind of crazy to me. But um that
one surprised me. And then um yeah, that
was it.
>> Freaking the Eagles. I mean
it's like they stumble into it too. Like
Howie Roseman isn't a genius because he
took Mai Lemon at 20. Why does the
league keep doing this guy so many
favors? Like they're trying to set him
up to look good. Mai Lemon should not
have fallen to 20 at the end. I know.
>> We said so many time I I love the Jordan
Tyson pick. Um but if the if Jordan
Tyson had gone seventh and the Saints
took Mai Lemon at eight, I probably
wouldn't even hate that. I We said a lot
of times
>> I would have liked that
>> move down to that we wanted the Saints
to trade down because Lemon was going to
go in the teens. Like I would have liked
to see the Saints trade down to 12 and
then take Lemon or T trade down to 15
and then take Lemon. The Eagles got him
at 20. That's ridiculous. The league has
got to stop just handing these like
that's the best pick of the draft
because he fell into their laps and you
know the other 19 teams should be
ashamed. And and similar to Ruben Bane
and Tampa Bay, I did not want the Saints
to take Bane. I was a little scared at
eight. Um but Tampa Bay getting him at
15, it's like oh crap, now they got to
face him twice in the division.
M Lemon going in the top 10. I wouldn't
have batted the knee. If the Saints took
him to eight, I would have been on here
talking about, hey, like he fits, he
adds a lot like that the the value of
this type of player, we've seen it just
just boom. Uh Ibuka, JSN, like all these
guys that Aman Ross St. Brown, like
these are guys that give your like we
would have been, hey, look, like the
league is changing. You got to look at
these guys. and they they just all watch
this happen and then they're like, "Let
this guy fall to 20 to the freaking
Eagles who are giving up their receiver
and now they just got the the perfect
replacement." Like the fix is in, man.
Like it's just insane how like this
can't keep happening for him.
>> It's unbelievable. It's unbelievable.
>> I hate it, man. I hate it so much. Like
it's just it's see like it's just he's
always there to take advantage of every
opportunity. It's insane uh that it
keeps going. Well, uh,
now that we're, uh, Yeah. Yeah. Uh,
let's just move on to the next topic
presented by Aaron Rose. What, what do
the Saints need to do most on day two?
>> I mean, it's easy to say defense, and
that's true. I mean, I I I'm I'm still
best player available. It's why I didn't
want them to trade up. Like, get talent.
If they go guard and tight end tonight,
fine. I mean, like, just stockpile
talent. Make home run draft picks. Make
picks. I can't believe this guy fell.
Um, but it's easy to look at defense and
I'm still there were three positions
that felt like the must be addressed.
One was wide receiver. One is frankly
four defensive end and defensive tackle.
But one way or another the defensive
line and then the other one is a
secondary whether it's a corner or a
safety who can play the star position.
Those those and and I like the talent. I
mean if you look at the best available
list right now it's mostly defensive
lineman and defensive backs. So, feels
like a good spot to be picking at 42.
Um, if if they hadn't taken uh Tyson,
I'd be talking about Denzel Boston here
or Chris Bell here. Uh, I feel like they
could scratch that off the list tonight.
Uh, but uh yeah, there's some intriguing
defensive lineman and DBs still
available. That that would probably feel
like the one that that slots in and
makes you feel like, hey, they nailed
it.
Yeah, I I'm I'm I'm
think today you if you tell me they can
make two picks to close the day and you
go into the the day three, pass rusher,
offensive lineman. I think if you give
me those two things and then day three
just defense, defense, defense, defense,
defense is kind of what I would like to
see there. I think running back's
probably on their board in day three, I
I would I would probably prefer not to
do that. I'm an Alvin, you know, bring
him back, keep keep him going, keep a
rolling guy. um more than you know one
of the Penn State guys or whatever. Um
obviously you got to weigh longterm
verse short term whatever like I just
think there's a lot to give there and I
think this team has a chance on offense
and and I think there are chances higher
with Alvin in the the perfectly crafted
role. Um, so I'm for that. But yeah, I
think I think pass rusher and O line are
the two things that I would really like.
And I don't even necessarily know that
they need to replace anyone on the but I
want the competition and I want I want a
very strong backup just given the injury
histories and all that stuff there. I
know Raidens is on the team. Um, but
another one would would be very nice to
have, I think.
>> Yeah.
>> Lynon Young ain't back, is he? He left.
>> I think he's TBD, right? Like I don't
think he's ressigned, but I don't think
he's resigned elsewhere yet.
>> Yeah. So, I mean like there there's a
need for that swing player. Awesome.
Richards is there, but yeah, I mean it
it could be it could be inside or
outside. Just give me an offensive
lineman of of some form or fashion to
add to the mix.
>> Um, let me ask you this. This would be
number one on my list. Peter Woods
almost slipped into round two and I was
getting a little excited about that
thought. I I think my number one choice
if it existed would be a pass rushing
defensive tackle. Uh, Kade Mcdonald is
is really enticing. Kristen Miller
somewhat enticing. They're both more run
stuffing defensive tackles. Is there a
pass rushing defensive tackle or or does
that does that have to be uh put that on
the agenda for next year?
>> I want the edge player.
>> Yeah.
>> Get like let Vernon let Vernon trust it.
If you believe in him, trust it.
>> Yeah. Vernon and Brazique can both fill
that fill that need.
>> Yeah. Um did we talk about corner? Not
necessarily, but uh real quick before
you said Edge, uh uh do you have
favorites? There are a few out here.
Zion Young's still out there. Cashes, we
love R. Mason Thomas.
>> Talking about Edge guys. Yeah, I like
all that. Like just any g get I mean
we've been Arm Mason the whole way, so
just land the plane. Like if I got to
pick one, pick him. Um corner. Look, I I
I know we're we're going to debate this
on the site today. And I I'm I'm not
against corner, but I'm not necessarily
forcing a corner pick cuz I I don't know
that I need a guy that's the equal of
the other two that are already on the
team. If I can like I would rather draft
a position where I feel like I can get
better. Now, if it's
>> even and there's not the edge guy, I
think I think corner moves up for me,
but if I got to weigh the two in there,
like I got to go edge because I think I
think my edge situation is more dire
than my corner situation. Um, so I I
don't I don't need another, you know,
another Quincy or Cool. Like I only
draft that if you feel like you can get
better.
I probably stay away from McCoy. I think
>> I don't know where the value is, but
boy, that like
>> I don't even know what it is, but you
say knee plug and I say nah. Like I'm
good on that.
>> I agree. It's a little different than
the Jordan Tyson conversation.
>> Yeah.
>> I will say this about corner though. I
think Avon Terrell uh could have been a
first round pick. I think whoever gets
him, somebody's gonna give them an A+
day two draft grade. And then uh you
know, I've been talking about D'Angelo
Ponds and then Keonte Scott still out
there. All three of those guys could
plug right into your nickel spot. And
that is a need. So I wouldn't hate that.
I wouldn't hate it, but I agree. Uh an
edge rusher would be the thing that
makes me feel like the most like, you
know, hit the ground running of any of
these picks.
>> Well, I'm going to say this, like I
think slot weapon's a little bit
different to me than just like another
outside corner. If you tell me like the
slot weapon like the and that could be
that could be the safety if you if you
view Pawns as that if you view Kyle Lois
as is that type of player. Uh I'm cool
with it. I'm definitely cool with that
type of type of player. But like just
like another outside corner that's at
the same level as the other guys. I feel
good about Ike is is my third option at
that spot. Just
>> on the outside.
>> Yeah, on the outside. No, if it's like
an improvement, yes. Like if you feel
like you can improve the outside,
improve the outside. Um Keonte Scott uh
is a guy who ran the 433 at his proday
for Miami and uh um he basically plays
DB like like a linebacker. Uh he could
almost be called a safety instead of a
corner. But the best Scott, he wears
number zero. Was the last team at time
NFL team took took two players with
their first two picks that both wore
number zero. Let's keep it going.
>> There you go. There you go. Um yeah, I I
the edge guy though, man. DN DN wide
receivers is kind of how we've been
hoping this thing would would fall and
we might as well just ride it out until
uh until the end. Uh next one presented
by Hardh High Punch Strawberry Whiskey
and Chilton County Peach. What do you
think we learn about Alvin and Kemp
tonight? Does does anything change for
him? And I was a little bit just just to
preface this, I I was a little bit
surprised just kind of by the the answer
of that of of Mickey. Um, and I think
it's realistic that their draft plans
could change things for either one of
these guys and he acknowledged that what
they do could change the plans for these
guys.
>> He's he's tiptoed at that. We had heard
that behind the scenes, but Mickey's
just openly saying it now. Like, let's
see what our roster looks like and then
we'll decide if we want those guys or
not. I mean, it's basically what he
said. And and with Cam, I think we I
don't know if I want to say we know um
because we're not getting
minute-by-minute updates. We've gotten a
sense that the CAM offer is kind of on
the table no matter what. Cam, if you
want to come back and play for this
offer, you can. And if they had drafted
Arville Reese last night, if they draft
our Mason Thomas tonight, maybe Cam will
say, you know what, I don't need to be a
fourth defensive end for this team. Uh
I'm gonna I'm going to go elsewhere. And
if Cam's like, "Well, I'll be the third
defensive end for this team. I'll
probably get my snaps. Maybe he takes
it." I mean, that that in that sense
very real. Whether they get that edge
rusher or not could determine if Cam
wants to come back. And I think it might
be true with Alvin. I don't know that
Alvin has an offer on Alvin's under
contract. I I feel like at some point
they're going to ask Alvin to take a pay
cut and they might be waiting. If they
ended up with Jeremiah Love, they might
not have even asked Alvin to take a pay
cut. They just might have moved on. But
I I feel like if they don't draft a
running back tonight, if they draft one
in the fourth round, I don't think that
affects Alvin. They don't draft a
running back tonight, I think they maybe
open those talks. All right, you see
where we're at. Let's see where you're
at. Um, so I do think I I do think both
of those positions, if they get past
tonight without filling edge rusher and
running back, I think it's more likely
those guys are back. If they fill one of
those positions tonight on night two, I
I think they can say goodbye to those
guys.
I I find it very interesting the way
they're talking about Alvin considering
that Alvin's under contract and they owe
him $3 million free agent.
>> Yeah, they owe him $3 million. What do
you mean like Alvin's plans are going to
change? If I'm Alvin, my plans are well,
if your plans change, you got to pay me
>> my check.
>> Yeah, I'm not asking to I'm not leaving
for you. You got to give me $3 million.
Like that that would be my my approach.
And then kind of the the public stance
on it I feel like undermines the ability
to maybe come to like a and I think he's
I think the way Alvin thinks about the
world is like so like I I don't think
this is probably going to affect
anything because I think he very much is
like a I'm going to compartmentalize
this. I'm not going to pay attention to
this. I don't care what anybody thinks
about anything. But man, like that's a
that's a potentially risky way to to set
up a let's come to a mutual bene a
mutually beneficial agreement and uh you
know, let's let's end this thing
harmoniously. I was just surprised by it
because like Yeah, they're talking about
him like, well, he has a decision. Well,
no, he doesn't. He already signed and
he's owed $3 million.
>> It's wild.
>> It's true. It's true. I mean, when they
keep saying he has a decision to make,
my guess for a while was, oh, they must
have asked him to take a pay cut. But
that it sounds like they're they're like
telling him telling him you go do you
and we'll call you in May which is just
crazy. It's crazy. But best
>> that is what's happened.
>> I know. Best case scenario for this team
though I think is that they don't draft
a running back and and and Alvin becomes
like a bonus. Like I mean he's more than
a bonus. He was our number one player on
the team 10 months ago. Uh and and
they're treating him like he's Lap right
now. But I hope he's laying you up for
this team. I'll feel a lot better about
the offense if Alvin Chimera is like an
extra piece.
>> I want him on the team. But I a I think
that he makes him better. Genuinely.
Genuinely, I think he makes him better.
I think you've built a team now where
you could just put him in a perfect role
and it just accentuates everything. He
still does a ton of stuff. Great. I
think he can be a great play. I think
the team's good now. Uh I think that
that helps. Like you can block now
probably. That probably helps. And then
also
he's a plus to the team. He's not a
minus to the team. He's a plus to the
team. You have a Chan. You have other
options at running back, man. Just like
like it would just be cool to see him
end his career here and have like the
nice sendoff. Like he he's an important
guy to this team, to this city. He's
chosen to stay here. He should have
dipped years ago. He shouldn't have
signed the other contract. He'd be a
Hall of Famer right now had he left. He
chose to stay here and battle it out.
And you know, I I think he he genuinely
fought for what he thought was good for
the team. Like during hard times, he was
the voice for the for the voiceless. He
he spoke for the fans. Like he really
did. Uh he acted on it. Um I don't know,
man. Like I just like to see him like
end it the right way. Both of them, him
and Cam, because I don't think they're
minuses to either team. Um to to either
side. I you know, I think you need to
add another pass pressure. I think Cam
can be in a good role. I think he's a
contributor. I I just want to see both
those guys end it right. And you know
that that's uh that's like I've said a
million times. I I don't know that
that's the hard analytical
uh you know play GM approach, but that
that that's the uh you know the person
that grew up loving sports point of view
on things is that like you just want to
see some of these stories end right.
>> Yeah. You haven't filled every need on
the team. There's a couple needs where I
think you might have to dip back into
veteran free agency if you don't fill
them. There's nobody in veteran free
agency that would be anywhere close to
what Alvin and Cam could be. Like
they're not building your team long term
for the future, but they're way way way
more than filling in for a year or two.
It's not like Deviian Clowney and uh uh
uh Nick Chub. It's It's freaking Alvin
and Cam.
>> Yeah. And I don't think either one of
them are at a point where it's like sad,
>> you know? Like I don't think it's sad
like uh this is I think I think you can
get one more out of both guys and and
just I don't know kind of let it just I
don't know I I
they're in the right ro like if you get
another pass rusher I feel like both
these guys are in like the right spots
to come back to contribute to to end it
right and just let it go at that point.
Um we're going to hit a quick break and
we will be right back.
Are you ready to buy your first home?
Wondering if now is the right time to
refinance? Or maybe you're thinking
about getting into real estate? Whatever
play you're trying to run, the pros at
mortgage bros.money have the game plan.
If you are a firsttime buyer, the
mortgage bros will break down every loan
program, help you build a budget that
works, and even check if you qualify for
100% financing or down payment
assistance. They'll guide you every step
of the way. Because buying your first
home shouldn't feel like a Hail Mary.
Heard that rates have dropped and
thinking it's time to refi? Don't just
guess, get real answers. The mortgage
bros will review your situation for free
and tell you if it's time to make a move
or keep waiting for an even better rate.
And if you're ready to start investing
in real estate, don't let that old 20%
down myth stop you. The bros can show
you a home hack that might get you up to
three doors to rent with little to no
money down. Here's the best part. The
mortgage bros work with you for free.
You'll never pay them a penny. They're
not bankers, they're brokers. That means
if your loan doesn't close, they don't
get paid. So, they're just as invested
in getting you approved as you are.
Because, let's be honest, signing up for
a 30-year loan without a pro on your
team is like trying to run the offense
without a playbook. You don't need to
know every role in the mortgage game.
Your pros already do. So, go to mortgage
bros.money. That's mortgagebros.money.
And let the bros be your pros.
>> I got hurt in a car wreck. Why should I
get Gordon?
>> Because when you're hurt, you need
money. And I fight for the people of
Southeast Louisiana every day. I got a
client who injured their neck in a car
wreck $250,000.
Another client was hit by a big truck
and needed back surgery. I got them
$700,000 and they deserved every single
penny.
>> That's what I'm talking about. Why
wouldn't I get Gordon?
>> If you've been hurt in a car wreck, just
call me New Orleans. Get it done.
>> Call 504800888.
If you watch our show, you already know
the work that RV Masters does. They did
our van last off seasonason. I went up
there. I said, "Hey, look, I need power
for eight or nine hours. I need AC for
eight or nine hours, and I need
everything I need to run a broadcast
from this van. I'm going to drop it off,
and I want you to take care of it." And
they said, "All right, cool. We got
you." I went back up a couple weeks
later, job's done, looks amazing, works
amazing. Went through a whole entire
season, not a single issue, which is
absolutely unbelievable to me. They'll
do whatever you need. They dream bigger
than you dream and they can make your
wild dreams come to life. They have
preventative maintenance. They have
service packages for your RVs, your AC,
your generators. They specialize in
solar and lithium upgrades, satellite
TV, and Starlink. If you wreck your
vehicle, they'll get you fixed, too.
Whatever you need, they got you. That's
rv-masters.com.
They'll get you right. Whether you're a
local New Orleian or a fan in town for
the game, get your pre and postgame
fired up at Aaron Rose. Local chaos and
local love for the black and gold. Wake
up and live with daily drink specials,
mimosas, screwdrivers, buddy Marys, and
hot or frozen Irish coffees. All just
three or four dollars between 10:00 a.m.
to 2 p.m. Aaron Rose, half a block from
Bourbon Street in the French Quarter,
811 Ki Street. Attention football fans,
don't let pest and termites invade your
home field. Trust the team at Red Pest
Solutions to tackle those unwelcome
visitors. Call the Red Man today for
unbeatable pest and termite control.
Score peace with no pest. Visit
redpest.com. That's reddp s.com.
Welcome back to New Orleans. Football
presented by Loft 18. Our question of
the day is presented by Gordon Mccernin,
Injury Attorneys. If you need help, make
sure you get Gordon. For the question of
the day, we are going to answer the
question, who would you take in the uh
in the in the second and third rounds,
we're going to run a little simulation
here on the mockdraft simulator. Uh we
got a little bit of of movement here.
McCoy goes at 33. Terrell 34, Emanuel
McNeel Warren at 35. Cleveland takes
advantage of the board with the big
double dip at wide receiver taking
Denzel Boston. Kansas City takes Jacob
Rodriguez, the linebacker. Kaden
McDonald, Dline to Cincy. Um, they're
stacking up on Dlineman right now. So,
we kind of got an interesting scenario
here. Zion Young is on the board.
>> Yeah,
>> our Mason Thomas is on the board. CJ
Allen's on the board. I don't like I I'm
still not taking the linebacker here. Um
wide receiver obviously isn't the need
for me, man. I'm going to start how we
how we're going to, you know, I want I
want to finish how we started and we
kind of started on our Mason Thomas. We
kind of came to a consensus on him. We
both like him.
For me, he's the he's the guy here. He's
the guy I think we take here. Um we're
in the the final countdown. I think we
trust our board in our scouting to this
point. Didn't we did we do Tyson Thomas
at Loft 18? We did, right?
>> Yeah, we did.
>> People who came out saw us get rounds
one and two exactly right. I think
we're Wizards. Uh first of all, I forgot
to mention when we were talking about
DBs earlier, McNeel Warren, I think he's
going 33rd tonight. I didn't even talk
about him because uh uh I don't think
he's going to fall to the Saints at 42.
That's another good DB. There's a lot.
This is a This is traditionally a good
DB range of the draft, but the Saints
have taken advantage of that for many
years. So, good DBs here. But yeah, um
I'm an AR Mason Thomas guy. I've been
pushing for him for a while. I don't I
don't know if I pass up the gift of Zion
Young here, though. Um home run if the
Saints get the choice between those two
guys. I kind of want to lean Mason
Thomas so that people will watch this
segment later and be like, "Man, these
guys know their stuff because I don't
think Zion Young will fall that far."
But if they're both there, you you can
sell me on either one.
>> Yeah, I'm I'm I just got to go with the
guy, man. Like, I've I've watched him. I
like him. I think he's the right I think
he's the right player for their team. Uh
so, I would pick him here on this one.
We'll we'll see how it plays out in real
life. I mean, I I think the other
conversation you do have to have, and
again, this is one that I This is This
isn't a hamstring. We We talked about it
earlier in the show. This is not a
hamstring.
If McCoy's there, like I think you have
a conversation, like I said, based on
what we know, that's that's just one
where I'm like, I no, I can't do it. I
don't know enough about it. It scares
me. So, I would bypass him if he's
there. I think he I think if that knee
thing's real, he is going to be there.
And man, if he just keeps falling, I I
don't need to be the team to stop him.
If they do, we'll find out about it and
see what it is. But that that's one
where I'd be like, I don't know. Um the
upside could be amazing. They drafted
Ryan Ramchre with the bad knee and it
worked out for years. Um I just don't I
don't know if I can do that one.
>> Going to the Eagles where at some point.
>> Let's take R. Mason.
>> Mason, you good with it?
>> Yep.
R Mason, by the way, I mean, it's just a
new world for New Orleans. You know, the
6'2 240 pound pass rusher who is mostly
just a pass rusher, might be okay on run
defense. That won't be his strength. Uh
won't win double teams, but he'll get
around the edge. He has speed and power.
Like, we just we covered this team for
15 years where they ignored guys like
him. I'm ready to start seeing him in a
Saints uniform.
All right, Kyle Lewis just went, Serat
just went, so there's no uh, you know,
no no second guessing on any of that
stuff. Antonio Williams being here is
interesting. Zachariah Branch, I mean, I
I don't think we're going wide receiver,
>> although those guys are those guys are
both return specialists, too. So,
there's a little Rasheed Shahed to both
of their games. It's It's not completely
off the table.
>> Um, all right. Max Claire's there.
Igbson's there. Skyler Bell's there. Uh
where where you want to lean for this
one?
>> I like uh the Illinois edge rusher, too.
That that's pretty interesting that he
went to the third round. But uh click on
the DB tab
>> corner and then safety just to see who
fell here
and then safety.
>> Uh oh, you want safeties?
>> I'm just looking at both. I'm just
looking at both to see if any
>> Jaylen Kilgore, Bug Clark, Genesis
Smith. Who Who I I like Genesis Smith.
uh VJ Payne, uh Jacobe Thomas, uh Texas,
Lewis Moore, Bishop Fitzgerald, and then
at quarterback it's Igbenson, Malik
Mohamd, Julian Neil, Deon Moore,
Chandler Rivers, Dalen Everett, Will
Lee, and Takario Davis. Um I'll let you
make final call on this one. My guy
here,
>> I'm taking Sam Heck.
>> All right. Well, that's what I was going
to say. hit OT and interior offensive
line cuz you said that earlier. Uh we're
hitting a home run if we we get out of
there. Uh and I Yes, I do like Heck a
lot. Who do they have at uh OT?
Uh Dunker went. Huh? He never falls to
round three. Um
>> Crownover, Parker, Bowie, Cage, Casey,
Markel Bell, Trey.
>> I don't like any of those names better
than heck. I I'm with you. I'm with you.
I'm perfectly fine even though they have
defensive needs. Uh this we've got a
couple years to rebuild this roster. Uh
uh I have no problem. I I like Heck and
the value in round three. I'd feel
pretty good about them coming out with
an edge rusher and a guard.
>> All right. And then we're back on the
board here. Round four. Let's just run.
Holy shockas
is still like I would just take him at
this point.
>> I'm not going all the way through. Let's
let's just play out round four. We'll
end it after round four.
And then we're still on the board here.
See, I like I like this setup though,
man. Like I'm I'm just going to go I
would just go all defense here like the
rest of the way around that secondary
now. Although freaking stribbling.
Stribbling's not lasting this long. I
like dribbling, man.
>> You know what's in Well, I mean, I think
like they would probably go running back
in this range, too. Uh, at that point,
this is this is the scenario that we
just we just watch this play out.
>> Yeah.
>> And weird things happen in the draft all
the time.
>> This would be a scenario where I wonder
if if Cam Jordan would be like,
>> what else is out there because they just
drafted two and I don't know that
they're intending to, but like this
would be something that would
>> Good point
>> change a conversation.
>> Good point for sure.
>> Um, yeah, I'm a dealer's choice here on
this one. You want You want uh
scribbling?
>> Uh
>> you want to go running back? You want to
find another defensive player? Uh
>> give me a give me I mean let's
>> I do like Well, look, there's TJ Hall.
Haven't taken him yet. I like Kennedy,
too, though. Um I like all three of
those DBs on the board. That Oh, look at
that. We didn't get Sunny Styles. We get
Lorenzo Styles later. Um
take your pick of those first three
corners. I I I That's where the value
has fallen in this draft. I do like
dribbling, but I don't need two
receivers. And he's not going to fall
this far anyway.
>> I mean, I go I probably go Oregon here.
>> Yeah, I like him.
>> Um I'm I'm okay with any of them,
though. Yeah. Let There we go. And uh
we're going to get out of here on that.
We'll be covering the draft tonight.
Rounds two, rounds three. We'll be
updating this. Um maybe we'll hit an
updated one of these uh produce like a
little website special or something like
that just for uh day three when it comes
up. Appreciate you guys for tuning in.
We'll talk to you next time.